Babbitt, Bill; Collection apap204
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Advocacy, 1982-2016; Undated; 3; 1.17 cubic ft.
  - Buttons, Stickers and Bumper Stickers, Undated (Box 2 (3-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - Campaign to End the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (3-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - "The Closure Myth", Undated (Dvd 16)
  - Early Years, 1934-1961 - Bill Babbitt - Side A; Growing Up - Boston/Prov, U.S. Navy - Side B, Undated (Cassette 5)
  - "Fury to Forgiveness", Undated (Dvd 17)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (3-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - Sis. Winnie on Family History - Side A; Cape Verde Music - Side B, Undated (Cassette 6)
  - "Step by Step", Undated (Dvd 18)
  - Visitor Passes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Advocacy), Folder 6)